[
    {
        "lessonId": "timestamps",
        "title": "Timestamps",
        "exercises": [
    {
      "front": "Century",
      "back": "قَرْنٌ / قُرُونٌ",
      "back_hint": "Qarn / Qurūn"
    },
    {
      "front": "Year",
      "back": "سَنَةٌ / سَنَوَاتٌ",
      "back_hint": "Sanah / Sanawāt"
    },
    {
      "front": "Month",
      "back": "شَهْرٌ / أَشْهُرٌ",
      "back_hint": "Shahr / Ashhur"
    },
    {
      "front": "Week",
      "back": "أُسْبُوعٌ / أُسْبُوعَاتٌ",
      "back_hint": "Usbu' / Usubu'āt"
    },
    {
      "front": "Day",
      "back": "يَوْمٌ / أَيَّامٌ",
      "back_hint": "Yawm / Ayyām"
    },
    {
      "front": "Hour",
      "back": "سَاعَةٌ / سَاعَاتٌ",
      "back_hint": "Sā'ah / Sā'āt"
    },
    {
      "front": "Third",
      "back": "ثُلُثٌ / ثُلُثَاتٌ",
      "back_hint": "Thulth / Thulūth"
    },
    {
      "front": "Quarter",
      "back": "رُبْعٌ / أَرْبَاعٌ",
      "back_hint": "Rub' / Arbā'"
    },
    {
      "front": "Minute",
      "back": "دَقِيقَةٌ / دَقَائِقٌ",
      "back_hint": "Daqīqah / Daqā'iq"
    },
    {
      "front": "Second",
      "back": "ثَانِيَةٌ / ثَوَانٍ",
      "back_hint": "Thāniyah / Thāniyāt"
    },
    {
      "front": "Moment",
      "back": "لَحْظَةٌ / لَحَظَاتٌ",
      "back_hint": "Lahzah / Lahzāt"
    },
    {
      "front": "During",
      "back": "خِلَالَ",
      "back_hint": "Khilāl"
    }
  ]
  
    }
]